Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Like I said before, it's just for a month, we'll meet two or three times a week…
كما قلت سابقاً، الأمر سيستمر لمدة شهر فقط، وسنلتقي مرتين أو ثلاث مرات في الأسبوع...
And you just need to answer whenever I call.
وكل ما عليك فعله هو الرد على مكالماتي.
Okay.
تمام.
As long as you do what I ask, it shouldn't be too difficult.
طالما أنك تفعل ما أطلبه منك، فلن يكون الأمر صعباً للغاية.
Got it…
فهمتها…
Sir.
سيد.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Yes?
نعم؟
This and this…
هذا وهذا...
And that one too, please.
وهذا أيضاً من فضلك.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
By the way, how long are you going to keep calling me "sir"?
بالمناسبة، إلى متى ستستمر في مناداتي بـ"سيدي"؟
Hmm…
همم…
Then what should I call you?
إذن، ماذا أناديكِ؟
What do lovers usually call each other?
ماذا ينادي العشاق بعضهم بعضاً عادةً؟
Hmm…
همم…
Honey?
عسل؟
Ugh…
أوف...
Babe?
حبيبي؟
Or since your name is Minwoo…
أو بما أن اسمك مينوو...
How about "MyMin"?
ماذا عن "MyMin"؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Ba...
لا...
Let's just go with "babe".
لنستخدم كلمة "حبيبي" فقط.
Babe.
يا حبيبي.
And when we're alone, call me Mr. Minwoo.
وعندما نكون بمفردنا، نادني السيد مينوو.
I'll call you Mr. Yooha too.
سأناديك السيد يوها أيضاً.
Yes, babe.
نعم يا حبيبتي.
In this kind of situation, call me "Mr. Minwoo".
في مثل هذه الحالة، نادني "السيد مين وو".
Yes, Mr. Minwoo.
نعم، سيد مينوو.
JUNG Myeongcheol as Taeha
جونغ ميونغتشول بدور تايها
YOON Hyunkwon as Jaemin
يون هيونكوون بدور جايمين
LEE Suyeon as Suyeon
لي سويون بدور سويون
LEE Jaehyeop as Minwoo
لي جاي هيوب بدور مينوو
KIM Hyunseo as Yooha
كيم هيونسيو بدور يوها
"Sweetheart Service"
"خدمة الأحبة"
(Chapter 3: Cosmopolitan)
(الفصل الثالث: عالمي)
All of these are for you.
كل هذه الأشياء من أجلك.
I can't possibly accept this.
لا يمكنني قبول هذا بأي حال من الأحوال.
I'm giving them to you because you'll need them, so don't feel pressured.
أعطيكم إياها لأنكم ستحتاجون إليها، لذا لا تشعروا بالضغط.
But I still have so much to pay you back.
لكن ما زال عليّ الكثير لأرده لك.
This is all included in the contract.
كل هذا مشمول في العقد.
Okay.
تمام.
Two days later…
بعد يومين...
Are you free at 2 PM?
هل أنت متفرغ الساعة الثانية بعد الظهر؟
One moment, please.
لحظة من فضلك.
Yes, I'm free.
نعم، أنا متفرغ.
Great.
عظيم.
That day, just pretend to be my boyfriend in front of my friends.
في ذلك اليوم، تظاهرت فقط بأنني حبيبي أمام أصدقائي.
May I ask… what kind of friends?
هل لي أن أسأل... ما نوع الأصدقاء؟
Just do what you did with your boyfriend…
افعلي ما فعلتيه مع حبيبك...
I mean, the bartender yesterday.
أقصد، النادل بالأمس.
- He's not actually my boyfriend- - Thank you for waiting.
- هو ليس حبيبي في الحقيقة - شكراً لانتظارك.
I guess it doesn't matter…
أظن أن الأمر لا يهم...
Minwoo!
مينوو!
Minwoo.
مينوو.
Shall we go inside and take a look?
هل ندخل ونلقي نظرة؟
Wow…
رائع…
Wow, it's so beautiful.
يا له من جمال!
Hey, Minwoo…
مرحباً، مينوو…
Have you ever been to places like this?
هل سبق لك أن زرت أماكن كهذه؟
Do I look like someone who would?
هل أبدو كشخص قد يفعل ذلك؟
Minwoo.
مينوو.
Pick one.
اختر واحداً.
Huh?
هاه؟
If we're going to pretend to be a couple, shouldn't we at least have a matching item?
إذا كنا سنتظاهر بأننا زوجان، ألا يجب أن يكون لدينا على الأقل قطعة ملابس متطابقة؟
Let's pick something for each other.
لنختر شيئًا لبعضنا البعض.
I'll pay.
سأدفع.
Okay.
تمام.
This one.
هذا.
Oh god, that's so cute!
يا إلهي، إنه لطيف للغاية!
How did you know I like cute things?
كيف عرفت أنني أحب الأشياء اللطيفة؟
And for you, Minwoo…
أما أنت يا مينوو...
I'll choose this one.
سأختار هذا الخيار.
You want me to wear this?
هل تريدني أن أرتدي هذا؟
Isn't it super cute?
أليس هذا لطيفًا للغاية؟
I think it'll look perfect on you, Minwoo.
أعتقد أنه سيبدو مثالياً عليك يا مينوو.
Fine…
بخير…
Yooha!
يوها!
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Oh, hey.
أهلا.
Come on in, Jaemin.
تفضل بالدخول يا جايمين.
I know you've been busy preparing for jobs too, so I truly appreciate you helping out.
أعلم أنك كنت مشغولاً أيضاً بالتحضير للوظائف، لذا فأنا أقدر مساعدتك حقاً.
Oh, no problem.
لا مشكلة.
I should be thanking you, Taeha.
كان ينبغي عليّ أن أشكرك يا تايها.
Oh right, I'll get you an apron. Change first and I'll explain the work.
حسناً، سأحضر لك مئزراً. غيّر ملابسك أولاً وسأشرح لك العمل.
Okay.
تمام.
Oh, that looks good on you.
أوه، هذا يبدو جميلاً عليك.
All set.
كل شيء جاهز.
Are you feeling okay?
هل تشعر بأنك بخير؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Oh.
أوه.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Your face is beet red. Do you have a cold or something?
وجهك أحمر كالبنجر. هل أنت مصاب بنزلة برد أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Ah… is that so?
آه... هل هذا صحيح؟
I'm okay, though.
أنا بخير، على أي حال.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Then shall I show you around first?
هل أريك المكان أولاً؟
Please.
لو سمحت.
- Yes? - Are you watching?
- نعم؟ - هل تشاهد؟
Yes, nice to meet you.
نعم، تشرفت بلقائك.
It took me about two hours to get here.
استغرقت رحلتي إلى هنا حوالي ساعتين.
What would you like to drink?
ماذا تحب أن تشرب؟
Have you eaten?
هل أكلت؟
I'm dealing with a wisdom tooth at the moment.
أعاني حاليًا من ضرس العقل.
Ah…
آه...
Every time I come here…
في كل مرة آتي إلى هنا...
I see you here often, even though you seem quite busy yourself…
أراكِ هنا كثيراً، على الرغم من أنكِ تبدين مشغولة للغاية...
I'm back.
لقد عدت.
Come one in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Great job today, everyone.
عمل رائع اليوم يا جميعاً.
Hey.
يا.
How's the job? Is it going okay?
كيف حال العمل؟ هل تسير الأمور على ما يرام؟
Yeah, it's fine.
نعم، لا بأس.
What kind of part-time job did you do today?
ما نوع العمل الجزئي الذي قمت به اليوم؟
Um… I've taken on a steady gig as a fake boyfriend.
اممم... لقد حصلت على وظيفة ثابتة كحبيب مزيف.
For whom?
لمن؟
Some guy?
رجل ما؟
A guy?
رجل؟
Hey, don't tell Taeha, okay?
مهلاً، لا تخبروا تايها، حسناً؟
He's not some weird guy, right?
هو ليس شخصاً غريباً، أليس كذلك؟
I don't think he is.
لا أعتقد ذلك.
Hey, are you good with acting cute and stuff?
هل تجيد التصرف بلطف وما شابه؟
Huh? Why are you asking that?
هاه؟ لماذا تسأل هذا السؤال؟
I have to act like I'm really his boyfriend in front of his friends.
عليّ أن أتصرف أمام أصدقائه وكأنني حبيبه فعلاً .
I want to make a strong impression right away.
أريد أن أترك انطباعاً قوياً على الفور.
Ugh…
أوف...
Hmph…
همم...
Aing~!
أوه!
Come one~!
هيا بنا!
Hyuuuung~!
هيوووونغ~!
Ha!
ها!
Hey… thanks, and sorry too.
أهلاً... شكراً، وأعتذر أيضاً.
I'll take care of it from here.
سأتولى الأمر من هنا.
- Aing~! Come on~! - Hey, stop it.
- آينغ~! هيا~! - مهلاً، توقف عن ذلك.
Want me to help~?
هل تريدني أن أساعدك؟
Seriously, you…
بصراحة، أنت...
I thought you went abroad.
ظننت أنك سافرت إلى الخارج.
We left from Jeju and toured around Europe.
انطلقنا من جزيرة جيجو وقمنا بجولة في أنحاء أوروبا.
And I was hugging the toilet all day from the motion sickness.
وكنت أعانق المرحاض طوال اليوم بسبب دوار الحركة.
Seriously, he practically lived in the bathroom the whole time.
بصراحة، لقد كان يقضي معظم وقته في الحمام.
Oh? Hey, Minwoo! Long time no see. Didn't expect you to show up.
أوه؟ مرحباً مينوو! لم أرك منذ مدة طويلة. لم أتوقع ظهورك.
It's so hard to see your face these days.
من الصعب جداً رؤية وجهك هذه الأيام.
Who's that next to you? A friend?
من هذا الذي بجانبك؟ صديق؟
Ah…
آه...
He's my boyfriend.
إنه حبيبي.
Say hi.
قل مرحباً.
Hello, I'm Son Yooha.
مرحباً، أنا سون يوها.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
- Alright alright, have a seat. - Hello.
- حسناً حسناً، تفضل بالجلوس. - أهلاً.
Make yourself comfortable.
اجلس براحة.
That looks cute. Where did you buy it?
هذا يبدو لطيفاً. من أين اشتريته؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Hey, Minwoo, what is this?
مينوو، ما هذا؟
Did you always like this kind of stuff?
هل كنت تحب هذا النوع من الأشياء دائماً؟
Why? It looks good on him…
لماذا؟ لأنه يبدو جميلاً عليه...
Isn't it normal for couples to have matching items?
أليس من الطبيعي أن يمتلك الأزواج قطع ملابس متطابقة؟
Matching items?
هل توجد قطع متطابقة؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Man, I've been so busy lately…
يا رجل، لقد كنت مشغولاً للغاية مؤخراً...
Preparing for our wedding and all.
نستعد لحفل زفافنا وكل شيء.
But seriously, getting married… it's no easy business.
لكن بجدية، الزواج... ليس بالأمر السهل.
It's not something a person can do alone.
ليس هذا شيئًا يمكن للشخص القيام به بمفرده.
It's tough work.
إنه عمل شاق.
Minwoo, shouldn't you get married too?
مينوو، ألا يجب عليك الزواج أيضاً؟
Yeah, now is the perfect time to start thinking about it.
نعم، الآن هو الوقت المثالي للبدء بالتفكير في الأمر.
Guys like you staying single these days?
هل ما زال الرجال مثلك يفضلون العزوبية هذه الأيام؟
People will give you weird looks, you know?
سينظر إليك الناس نظرات غريبة، أتعلم؟
"Just do what you did with your boyfriend…
"فقط افعلي ما فعلتيه مع حبيبك..."
I mean…
أعني…
With the bartender yesterday"
مع النادل أمس"
Of course.
بالطبع.
But Minwoo and I are so happy together now.
لكن أنا ومينوو سعداء جداً معاً الآن.
Minwoo, tell them…
مينوو، أخبرهم...
About how you burned the onions while cooking yesterday.
بخصوص كيف أحرقتِ البصل أثناء الطهي أمس.
- The onions… - Yeah.
- البصل... - أجل.
Ah, right…
آه، صحيح...
The onions…
البصل…
Wait, are you two living together?
لحظة، هل تعيشان معاً؟
Cooking?
طبخ؟
Minwoo cooks?
مينوو يطبخ؟
Of course! Minwoo is such a great cook…
بالتأكيد! مينوو طباخ ماهر للغاية...
And a great catch, too~
وصيد رائع أيضاً!
How long has it been since we've been this lovey-dovey?
كم مضى من الوقت منذ أن كنا بهذا القدر من الحب والود؟
Babe?
حبيبي؟
- Babe… - Lovey-dovey?
- حبيبي... - هل أنتما متحابان؟
So are you two getting married soon?
هل ستتزوجان قريباً؟
Marriage?
زواج؟
We should, someday.
ينبغي علينا ذلك، يوماً ما.
But honestly, we're so happy even without it.
لكن بصراحة، نحن سعداء للغاية حتى بدونها.
We're just crazy about being with each other.
نحن مغرمان ببعضنا البعض.
Right, babe?
أليس كذلك يا حبيبتي؟
Wow, Minwoo, you've really changed since you started dating.
واو، مينوو، لقد تغيرت كثيراً منذ أن بدأت المواعدة.
- I've never seen you like this. - You two look happy.
- لم أركما هكذا من قبل. - تبدوان سعيدين.
Hey, how's your wedding prep going?
مرحباً، كيف تسير استعدادات زفافك؟
Oh gosh, he's been obsessed with losing weight lately.
يا إلهي، لقد أصبح مهووساً بفقدان الوزن مؤخراً.
Yooha, great job today.
يوها، عمل رائع اليوم.
They'll take care of spreading the rumor for us now.
سيتولون هم نشر الشائعة نيابةً عنا الآن.
That was a huge success.
كان ذلك نجاحاً باهراً.
You can go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
If you need anything else, feel free to contact me anytime.
إذا احتجت إلى أي شيء آخر، فلا تتردد في الاتصال بي في أي وقت.
Taeha, time to go home.
تايها، حان وقت العودة إلى المنزل.
Yeah, let me just finish this.
أجل، دعني أنهي هذا.
What's with that outfit?
ما قصة هذه الملابس؟
Did you just buy that?
هل اشتريت هذا للتو؟
Oh, this? Someone gave it to me.
أوه، هذا؟ لقد أعطاني إياه أحدهم.
Who?
من؟
Looks pretty nice…
يبدو جميلاً جداً…
Just a friend.
مجرد صديق.
I'm going to the bathroom real quick.
سأذهب إلى الحمام بسرعة.
"Sweetheart Service"
"خدمة الأحبة"
Have you subscribed to STRONGBERRY channel yet?
هل اشتركت في قناة سترونغبيري حتى الآن؟
What? You haven't?
ماذا؟ لم تفعل؟
Then do it right now, please.
إذاً، افعل ذلك الآن، من فضلك.
Hit that subscribe button.
اضغط على زر الاشتراك.
Click.
انقر.
Please and thank you.
من فضلك وشكراً.
Sorry~
معذرةً~